twistimage.com 2008-09-15

# Privacy Policy - Twist Image

Twist Image is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information in ways other than that disclosed in this statement. Twist Image may collect information from our users at various different points on our website.

## Log File

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Twist Image, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware, when they leave our site, to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we shall notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. Your consent by using our site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Twist Image. Twist Image welcomes your questions and comments about privacy, please e-mail them to [support@twistimage.com](mailto:support@twistimage.com).

* * *
